Baran, is this you?
It began after a bad case of viral meningitis when I was five.
They tried every anti-seizure medication,
but I still had episodes every few months or so.
No one's ever noticed before. They just think I'm thoughtful.
Are you driving?
I couldn't until laser ablation
to my left temporal lobe 12 years ago.
Between that and the Keppra, I've been seizure-free,
cleared by Neurology to drive and to work as an attending.
How long, uh, between the seizure you had today and the last one?
It's been well over a year.
But I had two today.
I don't know why.
It could be sleep deprivation, new job stress.
I--I haven't had to deal with Peds cases since Afghanistan.
What are your options now?
up my Keppra
or maybe try one of the newer anti-seizure meds.
But if that doesn't work, I'm left with two choices--
um, a temporal lobectomy, which could impair my speech,
or get a neuromodulation device,
which can sense and stop the seizures almost immediately.
You need to disclose this.
I know. I have a plan.
Hey, Robby, Dana's looking for you. She's in Peds.
Yeah, OK, I'll be right there.
Sounds like you're needed in Peds, and I have patients to see.
Robby, pregnant woman with severe headache
on her way in by ambulance.
Find Abbot or a night shift resident.
Need you to turn out your pockets.
OK. Show me your hands.
Come here often?
What's going on?
Oh, sorry--false alarm. We thought she spiked a fever,
but it was the wrong chart from our analog hell.
You know anybody who might consider kinship adoption?
- Doctors and nurses qualify. - Don't look at me.
Hey, can your staff keep an eye on Dr. Al-Hashimi until she leaves?
Why?
Uh, because I think she's tired, and I don't want her to make any mistakes.
Oh, great advice. Maybe you should take it.
Yeah. I'm gonna go get some fresh air.
Grab some for me while you're out there.
Your lungs wouldn't know what to do with it.
- Screw you! - In front of the baby? Nice.
Yeah.
We are the night crawlers.
We deal with the weirdest and the wildest because...
We are the weirdest and the wildest of them all.
That is right, and tonight, they are really gonna be crawling. Now go get some!
Sorry to wake you.
I--I was thinking.